Crusade for Opportunity Records
Crusade for Opportunity Records
- Financial files
  - Payroll department, 1966 (Box 337)
  - Payroll fund, general journal ledger, 1966-1967 (Box 337)
  - Payroll for personnel, 1966 (Box 337)
  - Payroll ledgers, 1966 (Box 370)
  - Payroll printouts, 1966 (Oversize 1)
  - Payroll register, 1967 (Box 371)
  - Payroll register, 1967 (Box 372)
  - Payroll rosters, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 337)
  - Payroll rosters, 1967-1968; 4 folders (Box 338)
  - Payroll systems, 1964-1966 (Box 338)
  - Pay stubs, 1965 (Box 369)
  - Petty cash, 1966 (Box 338)
  - Petty cash reimbursements, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 338)
  - Petty cash reimbursements, 1967 (Box 339)
  - Petty cash reports, 1966 (Box 339)
  - Postage meter receipts, 1965 (Box 339)
  - President's Committee on Juvenile Delinquency
    - Audit exceptions, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Bank reconciliations, 1964-1967 (Box 360)
    - Budget, 1966 (Oversize 1)
    - Budgets, 1964-1965 (Box 339)
    - Budget reports, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Budget revisions, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Contract, City School District and CFO, 1967 (Box 339)
    - Contract, Community Chest and CFO, 1964 (Box 339)
    - Contract with Community Chest, 1965-1966 (Box 339)
    - Correspondence relative to Action Area Planning contract, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Correspondence relative to Community Chest contracts, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Correspondence relative to school contracts, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Deposits, 1964-1965 (Box 360)
    - Discussion drafts, budgets, 1964-1965 (Box 339)
    - Final report, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 360)
    - Financial reports, 1965 (Box 339)
    - Financial reports, 1965 (Box 340)
    - Financial statements, 1964-1965; 2 folders (Box 340)
    - First Trust and Deposit Company, check stubs, 1965-1966 (Box 340)
    - General ledgers, 1964-1966 (Box 340)
    - Grant, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Grant budget, 1965; 2 folders (Box 340)
    - Revised budgets, 1965 (Box 340)
    - Summer program, budget, 1965 (Box 340)
    - Syracuse City School District contract agreement, 1964 (Box 340)
    - Work papers, 1965
  - Printing estimates, 1964 (Box 340)
  - Purchases department, memos and correspondence, 1967 (Box 340)
  - Purchasing correspondence, 1965 (Box 340)
  - Purchase Orders
    - Air Photo Supply, 1965 (Box 340)
    - American Seating Co, 1965 (Box 340)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 340)
    - Smith Corona Marchant, 1964-1965 (Box 340)
    - Standard Office Supply, 1964-1965 (Box 340)
    - Superior Electric Co., 1965 (Box 340)
    - Superintendent of Documents, Government Printing Office, 1964-1965 (Box 340)
    - Syracuse Blueprint Co., 1964-1965 (Box 341)
    - Syracuse Letter Co., 1965 (Box 341)
    - Syracuse Restaurant and Supply Co., 1964-1965 (Box 341)
    - United Rent-Alls, 1965 (Box 341)
    - Voided numbers, 1964-1965 (Box 341)
  - Receipts, 1966-1967 (Box 341)
  - Receipts for checks, 1966 (Box 341)
  - Refunding, 1967 (Box 341)
  - Regular program, budget, 1967 (Box 341)
  - Reproductions, finance office, 1967 (Box 360)
  - Requisitions, 1965 (Box 341)
  - Requisitions - hold, 1964 (Box 341)
  - Request for office supplies, 1967 (Box 341)
  - Request for quotation, supplies, 1966-1967 (Box 341)
  - Salary sheets, 1965
  - Signature book for staff payroll checks, 1966 (Box 341)
  - Signature book for NYC payroll checks, 1966 (Box 341)
  - Staff files (Box 341)
    - Murray, John files, Financial Director
      - Addressograph - multigraph, 1966 (Box 341)
      - Administration, 1966 (Box 341)
      - Administrative guidelines, 1966 (Box 341)
      - Annual report, 1965-1967; 2 folders (Box 341)
      - Audit files, 1965-1966 (Box 341)
      - Bank, 1965 (Box 341)
      - BAT contract - extra copies, 1965 (Box 341)
      - Berry, Theodore, Director, Community Action Program, correspondence, 1965 (Box 341)
      - Bill Smith, memos, 1966-1967 (Box 341)
      - Bill Streets, correspondence, 1967 (Box 341)
      - Bill Streets, memos, 1966 (Box 341)
      - Budget, 1963 (Box 341)
      - Budget forms for neighborhood centers, 1967 (Box 342)
      - Budgets, OEO, 1965 (Box 342)
      - Bureau of Work Programs, 1967 (Box 342)
      - Catholic Schools, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Cathy Stepanek personnel file, 1964 (Box 342)
      - Central CFO, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Chamber of Commerce, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Community Action Program application, 1966; 2 folders (Box 342)
      - CAP for fiscal year June 30, 1967 (Box 342)
      - Community Chest, contributions and deductions, 1965 (Box 342)
      - Community Chest and Council, retirement plan, 1964 (Box 342)
      - Community Progress, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 342)
      - Computer, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Consultants, 1965 (Box 342)
      - Consumer education, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Contract list, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Contributions to CFO (in-kind), 1966; 2 folders (Box 342)
      - Corrective reading, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Credit union, 1966 (Box 342)
      - Curriculum Materials Development Center, 1966; 2 folders (Box 342)
      - Data processing, 1965 (Box 343)
      - Dave Lindberg correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 343)
      - Day files, 1966; 2 folders (Box 343)
      - Department of Health, Syracuse, 1967 (Box 343)
      - Disability insurance, 1966 (Box 343)
      - East Side, 1966-1967 (Box 343)
      - Ellis Bert memo, 1967 (Box 343)
      - Employment - refunding, 1966-1967 (Box 343)
      - The Equitable Life Assurance Society, correspondence, 1967 (Box 343)
      - Far East Side, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Far East Side Study Center, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Ferro, Frank, District Director, correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 343)
      - Follow up, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Form approvals, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Foundations, 1965 (Box 343)
      - 4-H, 1967 (Box 343)
      - General file, 1966-1967 (Box 343)
      - GSA Autos, 1966 (Box 343)
      - GSA - OEO, 1966-1967 (Box 343)
      - Hatch Act, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Health care, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Health, Education, and Welfare audit, 1967 (Box 343)
      - Jamesville program, 1965 (Box 343)
      - Job Corp recruitment, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Job descriptions - finance, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Job description - NYC trainee, 1966 (Box 343)
      - Job orders, 1967 (Box 344)
      - John Davis memo, 1965 (Box 344)
      - Home Aides of Central New York, 1967 (Box 344)
      - Hot summer money budget, 1966 (Box 344)
      - Indian Reservation, 1966-1967 (Box 344)
      - Information and referral, 1965 (Box 344)
      - Itemization, 1967 (Box 344)
      - Legal component, 1966 (Box 344)
      - LeMoyne HEP, 1966 (Box 344)
      - Lincoln Bank, corporate resolutions, undated (Box 344)
      - Lincoln Bank, correspondence, 1967 (Box 344)
      - Memos, 1966; 4 folders (Box 344)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967; 3 folders (Box 345)
      - Norman Hill memo, 1967 (Box 345)
      - NYC budget report forms, 1966 (Box 345)
      - NYC correspondence, 1965 (Box 345)
      - NYC general information, 1966 (Box 345)
      - New York State Division for Youth, 1965-1966 (Box 345)
      - New York State legislature, 1966 (Box 345)
      - Neighborhood organizations, 1966-1967 (Box 345)
      - Neighborhood study center, 1966 (Box 345)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity
        - Area planning service, 1965 (Box 345)
        - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 345)
        - General correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 345)
        - Information and referral, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Preschool language development, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Program development, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Re-entry, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Rehabilitation, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Special guidance, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Summer language development, 1966 (Box 345)
        - Teacher training, 1966 (Box 345)
      - OJT-BAT contract, correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 345)
      - OMAT bi-monthly report, 1966 (Box 360)
      - OMAT periodic reports, 1964-1966 (Box 345)
      - Onondaga Neighborhood Legal Service, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Paychecks, 1965-1966 (Box 346)
      - Personnel list, 1965 (Box 346)
      - Personnel policy manual regarding job descriptions, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Purchasing procedures, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Research (evaluation), 1966 (Box 346)
      - Request for consumable supplies, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Rita McVay, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Rural opportunities, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Salary surveys, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Senior staff memos, 1966-1967 (Box 346)
      - 66/491 correspondence, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Standard mileage chart, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Statement of grant award, President's Commission of Juvenile Delinquency, 1965-1966 (Box 346)
      - Summer programs, 1966 (Box 346)
      - Surplus property, 1963 (Box 346)
      - Syracuse University research corporation, CFO contract, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Tallman, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Tallman Neighborhood Center, 1966 (Box 346)
      - United Community Chest, retirement insurance and health insurance, 1964-1966 (Box 346)
      - War on Poverty, 1967 (Box 346)
      - Weekly schedule of meetings, 1967 (Box 346)
      - West Side, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 346)
  - Statements of corrected information, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 346)
  - Statements, paid invoices, 1965 (Box 346)
  - Stock requisitions, 1965-1966 (Box 346)
  - Stock requisitions filled, 1967 (Box 346)
  - Summer programs, equipment and supplies preliminary lists, 1967 (Box 347)
  - Summer programs, invoices (orange copies), 1967 (Box 347)
  - Supplies requests, 1967 (Box 363)
  - Tax exempt, out-of-town travel, 1967 (Box 347)
  - Telephone bills, Accounts payable (Box 347)
  - Telephone bills, OEO, 1965 (Box 347)
  - Telephone bills, OMAT, 1964-1965 (Box 347)
  - Telephone bills, PCJD, 1964-1965 (Box 347)
  - Telephone calls, 1964-1965 (Box 347)
  - Travel expense reports, 1966 (Box 347)
  - Vacation card, 1966 (Box 347)
  - Vendors (Box 347)
    - AB Dick, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Addressograph - Multigraph Co, 1964 (Box 347)
    - Al Edison, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Banning Stamp and Stencil Works, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Bills paid - miscellaneous A-Z, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Cole Typewriter, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Conference on Economic Progress, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Dixon's Messenger Service, 1963 (Box 347)
    - DIX Typesetting Company, Inc., 1963 (Box 347)
    - Eagle Lumber Company, 1963 (Box 347)
    - Eastern Air Lines, 1964 (Box 347)
    - Estabrook Printing, 1963-1964 (Box 347)
    - IBM Typewriter, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Jacobs, 1963 (Box 348)
    - J and FB Garrett Company, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Lee Cusack and Associates, 1963 (Box 348)
    - New York Telephone Company, 1964 (Box 348)
    - Kelly Girls, 1963-1964 (Box 348)
    - Paid, accounts receivable, 1964 (Box 348)
    - Parish Maintenance Supply, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Perry Office Supply, 1962-1964 (Box 348)
    - Raleigh and Munns, Inc. Insurance, 1964 (Box 348)
    - Smith Brothers, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Smith Corona Marchants, 1966 (Box 348)
    - Starr Platemaking Company, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Superior Electric Co., 1963 (Box 348)
    - Syracuse Blueprint Co., 1963 (Box 348)
    - Syracuse University Bookstore, 1963 (Box 348)
    - Travel, 1963 (Box 348)
    - WG Brown Sound, 1962-1963 (Box 348)
    - White Sales and Service, 1963 (Box 348)
  - Wage journals, 1966 (Box 373)
  - Wage and tax statements, 1965 (Box 348)
  - Weekly time record, 1966-1967 (Box 348)
- Legal files
  - Accident insurance policy, Chittenango Falls Day Camp, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Agency contracts, 1965 (Box 349)
  - Agreement to amend the On-The-Job training contract, amendment #1, 1967 (Box 349)
  - By-laws, 1965 (Box 349)
  - By-laws article I-IX, The Corporation, 1967 (Box 349)
  - By-laws CFO, 1966 (Box 349)
  - By-laws, revised, Aug 1966 (Box 349)
  - Certification for corporate sponsors, 1967 (Box 349)
  - CFO and Syracuse Central School District, contract, 1965-1966 (Box 349)
  - CFO-CSD contract, working papers, 1965 (Box 349)
  - CFO, OJT, BAT contract, 1966 (Box 349)
  - CFO, summary of legislation, 1965 (Box 349)
  - Comprehensive glass policy, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Contracts, rentals, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Contracts, rental equipment, 1967 (Box 349)
  - Corporate membership info, 1967 (Box 349)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Act of 1965 (Box 349)
  - Exemption organization certificate, undated (Box 349)
  - Fidelity bond, 1967 (Box 349)
  - Fire insurance policies, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Fire insurance policy, 323 Irving Ave, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Fire insurance policy, Temple and Oneida, 1966 (Box 349)
  - Form 12-2 NRP-insurance retirement "proof of death," blank, undated (Box 349)
  - Freund vs Crusade lawsuit, 1967; 3 folders (Box 349)
  - Freund vs Crusade lawsuit, 1967; 2 folders (Box 350)
  - Freund vs Crusade lawsuit, 1967 (Box 363)
  - Harty Real Estate, 1967 (Box 350)
  - Hatch Act, 1966 (Box 350)
  - High School accident insurance, 1966 (Box 350)
  - Insurance, day camp, East Side Center, 1967 (Box 350)
  - Insurance, general information, 1966 (Box 350)
  - Lease, 116 Huron Street, 1967 (Box 350)
  - Lease, 206 W. Water Street, 1965-1966 (Box 350)
  - Lease, 222-224 West Onondaga, 1967 (Box 363)
  - Lease data, 1964 (Box 350)
  - Legal action, 1967 (Box 363)
  - Legal services contract, 1966 (Box 350)
  - Legal suits vs Crusade, 1967 (Box 350)
  - Legislation, Economic Opportunity Amendments of 1966 (Box 350)
  - Libel suit, 1967 (Box 350)
  - New York disability, 1964-1965 (Box 350)
  - NY CAP 491/2, 1965 (Box 350)
  - OMAT contract #82-31-40, 1966 (Box 350)
  - OMAT #MDS9-64 contract, 1965 (Box 350)
  - OMAT supplemental contract, 1964 (Box 350)
  - The People of the State of New York vs Leroy Halloway, 1967 (Box 350)
  - Public law, Job Corps, 1964 (Box 351)
  - Recreation contracts, 1964-1965 (Box 351)
  - Tallman day camp, accident insurance, 1966 (Box 351)
  - Trustees, 1967 (Box 351)
  - Workman's Compensation, 1965-1967 (Box 351)
- Miscellaneous
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include grants, reports, brochures, directories, and memos; 5 folders (Box 351)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include educational materials, reports, and memos; 7 folders (Box 352)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include employment materials, press releases, financial, and job orders; 7 folders (Box 353)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include reports, memos, and financial; 6 folders (Box 354)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include legal material and notes; 6 folders (Box 355)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1964-1967; Materials include financial material, research data, committee minutes, reports, job orders, and miscellaneous maps; 6 folders (Box 363)